wannads.com 2017-06-06

# Wannads

##### 1\. Corporate information

1.1. In compliance with the provisions of Organic Law 15/1999 of 13 December on Personal Data Protection and Act 34/2002 of 11 July on Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce and the rest of the regulations related thereto, INNOVATIVE HALL MEDIA TECHNOLOGIES, S.L. (hereinafter INNOVATIVE HALL), a company with address in Calle Gordoniz 25, 1 Ext Izq; Bilbao, Vizcaya, Spain, with CIF B95694956 and company responsible for the Website, does hereby inform the users about the applications of its data protection policy.

##### 2\. Consent for the incorporation of personal data

2.1. INNOVATIVE HALL informs the Users that it complies with the data protection regulations in force and, specially, with Organic Law 15/1999 of 13 December on Personal Data Protection, Act 34/2002 on Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce and Royal Decree 1720/2007 of 21 December developing the Organic Law on Personal Data Protection. In compliance with the provisions of the aforementioned regulations, INNOVATIVE HALL states that they only collect the data which are strictly necessary to render the services derived from their activity and any other services and activities ascribed by the law, but they reserve the right to use the data in their databases to carry out statistical research on the registered users and the use they make of the Website.

2.2. To this end, the User entering any personal data in any electronic form or capture sheet provided in the Website is hereby informed and gives consent to the incorporation of the personal data supplied to the company by registering in the Website, completing any electronic form or sending any emails into the automated files owned by INNOVATIVE HALL, which are duly registered in the General Registry of Personal Data Protection.

2.3. Likewise, the User gives express consent to INNOVATIVE HALL for processing the data supplied during the inquiry, request or hiring of any service or any other operation carried out to access the information and the services provided by INNOVATIVE HALL through their Website and, where appropriate, maintaining the contractual relationship and sending offers or advertising and promotional communications by any means, including electronic means.

2.4. Finally, the User, by accepting the terms in this Clause, undertakes to comply with the obligations contained in this Privacy Policy while browsing and/or using the Website and to assume the scope of the guarantees given by INNOVATIVE HALL in this policy or any other which may be in force at any time.

2.5. INNOVATIVE HALL undertakes and guarantees the processing of personal data in keeping with the provisions of the aforementioned applicable regulations and those which may be in force at any time, as well as the utmost confidentiality with regard to the personal data supplied, by both INNOVATIVE HALL and the employees in the company which have or may have access to the aforementioned data.

##### 3\. Accuracy of the data provided

3.1. The User states that all the data provided are true and correct and undertakes to inform INNOVATIVE HALL about any changes which may take place.

3.2. Should the User supply any data from any third party, INNOVATIVE HALL does not take any responsibility for the compliance with the principles of information and consent and it is for the User to guarantee that he/she has previously informed the subject and obtained the consent to supply the data.

3.3. Besides, the supply of data is voluntary for the User but the failure to provide certain data or answers to questions which may be asked in the registration processes or in the electronic forms presented to the User may prevent the access to the services for which the personal data have been requested. INNOVATIVE HALL will in any case inform about whether the supply of the data is compulsory and/or necessary for the operation of the service.

##### 4\. Consent to the transfer of personal data

4.1. Due to the fact that some of the contents of the Website may have a commercial or advertising interest for trademarks, companies, businesses or any other third parties which may directly or indirectly hire INNOVATIVE HALL to carry out their advertising campaign, the User expressly gives consent and authorization to INNOVATIVE HALL to transfer the data contained in their files to those companies which manage the advertising campaign whose content the User has accessed through the Website, with the only guaranteed purpose of analysing the effects and performance of the campaign.

4.2. These transfers will be regulated in a Contract between INNOVATIVE HALL and the transferee in which the purpose of the transfer will be clearly specified.

4.3. Except for what is provided in Clauses 3.1. and 3.2. above, INNOVATIVE HALL will not disclose the personal information in its files to any third parties without the express consent of the User and will only use the data incorporated into the files to give the User access to the service and, if the User has given consent, to send commercial communications, information on the product and service and/or offers and promotions.

4.4. Likewise, INNOVATIVE HALL guarantees that they will not sell, hire or transfer in any profitable way the personal data of the Users or the means or addresses to contact them, except in those cases in which it may be necessary in order to render the service.

##### 5\. User rights

5.1. The User has the right to oppose to the processing of any data which are not essential to conclude the Contract and to their being used for any purpose other than the maintenance of their contractual relationship, such as processing for advertising purposes. If the User is not satisfied with the processing indicated in this policy, he/she may contact INNOVATIVE HALL so that his/her right of opposition to the processing becomes effective.

5.2. Likewise, the User may exercise the right of data access, rectification, cancellation and opposition through this email address support@wannads.com or the following mailing address: Calle Gordoniz 25, 1 Ext Izq; 48010 Bilbao (Vizcaya).

##### 6\. Access to other sites through the website

6.1. The service rendered by INNOVATIVE HALL contains or may contain links to third- party websites or media over which INNOVATIVE HALL has no control. This Privacy Policy is not applicable to the aforementioned websites. Therefore, any activity that the User may carry out in connection with the linked websites must be governed by their own terms, conditions, legal notices and privacy policy, for which INNOVATIVE HALL accepts no responsibility.

##### 7\. Sending offers and/or communications

7.1. In compliance with Act 34/2002 on Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce, INNOVATIVE HALL will only send offers or advertising and promotional communications by email or by any other equivalent electronic communication means to those Users who have expressly given their consent to receiving this type of communications. Notwithstanding this, by accepting the Terms and Conditions of the Website and this Privacy Policy, the Users expressly accept and authorize INNOVATIVE HALL to send them offers and advertising communications linked to the Website or to campaigns and/or activities included within it or disseminated through it.

7.2. The User may refuse to receive this type of communications at any time by sending a notice to INNOVATIVE HALL in the manner provided in Clause 5.2. above or by following the instructions which appear at the end of our emails.

##### 8\. Use of cookies

8.1. A cookie is a small text file which is kept in the computer of the User or in his/her mobile device and recovered in subsequent visits. There are two types of cookies, permanent and temporary (session cookies). Permanent cookies are stored as a file in the computer or mobile device for a period of time no longer than 12 months. Session cookies are stored temporarily and disappear when the browser is closed.

8.2. Cookies may be removed from the computer or mobile device by using the browser. To find out how to manage and remove cookies, just go to the “Help” tab in the browser to disable the cookies or, where appropriate, to receive a notice any time a new cookie is sent to the computer or mobile device. However, if the User disables the cookies he/she will lose some important features and functionality of the Website.

8.3. INNOVATIVE HALL informs the User that the Company uses cookies in the Website with the following purposes: (i) Permanent cookies to save the home page selection and to store User Data if he/she selects ‘Remember me’ at the start of the session. (ii) Session cookies when the User uses the product filter section and to check if the User has started a session.

8.4. Likewise, INNOVATIVE HALL uses cookies to identify, break down and classify the uses and accesses the Users may make of the Website and, specially, its various contents, in order to guarantee the correct operation of the usage points delivery system described in the Terms and Conditions of Use and the User. In any case, INNOVATIVE HALL uses cookies to improve and simplify the visits to the Website. In no case will cookies be used to store personal information to be disclosed to third parties.

8.5. INNOVATIVE HALL also uses cookies from third parties to collect statistical data in an aggregated manner through analysis tools such as Google Analytics. Cookies are used both in a permanent as well as temporary manner (session cookies).

8.6. By accepting the Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy, the User accepts and expressly consents to the use of Cookies by INNOVATIE HALL in the terms and for the purposes stated in this Clause 8.

##### 9\. Use of User's IP addresses

9.1. The User expressly authorizes INNOVATIVE HALL to store and use the IP addresses of application users in order to analyze trends and monitor the use of the applications as a whole. INNOVATIVE HALL does not associate IP addresses to any personally identifiable information.

##### 10\. Modification of the Privacy Policy

10.1. This Privacy and Personal Data Protection Policy may be modified, altered and/or replaced at any time, as a consequence of legislative or jurisprudential changes, changes in the criteria of the Spanish Data Protection Agency and/or any competent authorities or in keeping with the practices, traditions and customs of the sector, and due to any changes decided unilaterally by the management of INNOVATIVE HALL, either for the aforementioned reasons or not, and they undertake to provide the User, in a visible manner, with sufficient information regarding the modification which the Privacy Policy may undergo.

10.2. In any case, the User accepts that the Privacy Policy in force which he/she assumes and accepts as a consequence of his/her using and browsing the Website once the modification has been carried out is that which is posted in the Home Page of the Website itself and accessible for the User at all times.
